# **Ibrahim Samadzada**

LinkedIn | GitHub

Location: Azerbaijan, Baku Email: isamadzada@gmail.com | Mobile: +994558863884

### FLUTTER DEVELOPER

As a passionate **Flutter developer** with over **1 year and 2 months** of experience, I am seeking opportunities to further develop my skills in this field. I am dedicated to expanding my knowledge and expertise in Flutter and am enthusiastic about the potential for growth in this area.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages : Dart, Java Script, Type Script **Frameworks** : Flutter, React Native, Nest Libraries : Bloc, Provider, Redux

**Dev Tools** : Visual Studio Code, Git, BitBucket, Gitlab

## EXPERIENCE

# **FLutter-React Native Developer**

Feb 2023 - Present Code and Care Remote - Wilmington, DE

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications in a team using Flutter
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases
- Worked on new features as Voice-memo and Image uploading

**Flutter Developer** 

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023 Full time - Azerbaijan, Baku

Digital Legion

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications as solo developer using Flutter
- Worked with REST APIs to retrieve and display data from databases
- Implemented Subscription and Payment system
- Implemented Chat system to let User write messages to Jasper AI

**FLutter Developer** 

The Javachip

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

Full time - Azerbaijan, Baku

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications as solo developer using Flutter
- Worked with REST APIs and WebSockets to retrieve and display data from databases
- Implemented **Pedometer logic** to track user's steps
- Implemented Real-time chat to let user's chat with each other

### **EDUCATION**

French-Azerbaijani University

Azerbaijan, Baku

Bachelor in Computer Science

2020 - 2024

Université de Strasbourg Bachelor in Computer Science France, Strasbourg

2020 - 2024

# **PROJECTS**

2Walk Flutter, Bloc Play Market

- Developed a clean and modern mobile application using Flutter
- Maintained business logic using Bloc
- Utilized **Responsive design** to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented **Pedometer** to track user's steps

**AIZodiac** Flutter. Provider

- Developed a clean and modern mobile application using **Flutter**
- Maintained state management using **Provider**
- Utilized **Responsive design** to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented **Chat system** to let User write messages to Jasper Al

# LANGUAGES

Azerbaijani: Native languageRussian: Second Native

English : C1